Copeland railroad survey collection
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
Copeland railroad survey collection 1917-1958
G3701.P3 coll .C6 Copeland
H.H. Copeland and Son.
504 items
504 maps and supporting text
2 archival boxes 27 x 13 x 40 cm
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
H.H. Copeland and Son commissioned the materials that contain information about railroads in the United States from 1917 to 1958. The collection includes maps and data concerning railroad traffic density, tables on ton miles, freight density and traffic distribution, and other railway related tables and calculations. H. H. Copeland and Son were an investment house in existence from the late nineteenth century to around the mid 1950s. The materials were intended for their private use.
Provenance
No provenance information is available.
Access and Restrictions
The Copeland railroad survey collection collection is open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Geography and Map Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Scope and Content Note
Maps and data concerning railroad traffic density, tables on ton miles, freight density and traffic distribution, and other railway related tables and calculations. The materials date between 1917 and 1958. They cover railroads in the United States.
Arrangement
The Copeland railroad survey collection collection is organized in two series:
Series I Box 1 - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown to International and Great Northern Railroad
Series II Box 2 - Jersey Central Lines to Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
Organizations
Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad Company.; Ann Arbor Railroad Company.; Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railroad Company.; Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company.; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company.; Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Company.; Boston and Albany Railroad Co.; Boston and Maine Railroad.; Central Railroad of New Jersey.; Central Railroad of New Jersey.; Central Vermont Railroad Company.; Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad Company.; Chicago Great Western Railroad Company.; Chicago, Burlington & Quincy Railroad Company.; Chicago, Indianapolis & Louisville Railway Company.; Chicago, Milwaukee, and St. Paul Railway Company.; Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific Rail Road Co.; Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railway Company.; Cincinnati, New Orleans & Texas Pacific Railway Company.; Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago, and St. Louis Railway Company.; Colorado and Southern Railway.; Delaware and Hudson Railway Company.; Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company.; Denver and Rio Grande Railroad Company.; Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton Railroad.; Erie Railroad Company.; Florida East Coast Railway.; Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company.; Great Northern Railway Company (U.S.); H.H. Copeland and Son.; Illinois Central Railroad Company.; Kansas City Southern Railway.; Lehigh and New England Railroad.; Lehigh Valley Railroad Company.; Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Co.; Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company.; Maine Central Railroad Company.; Michigan Central Railroad Company.; Minneapolis & St. Louis Railroad.; Minneapolis, St. Paul & Sault Ste. Marie Railroad Company.; Missouri Pacific Railroad Company.; Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railway Company.; Mobile and Ohio Railroad Company.; Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railway.; New Orleans, Texas & Mexico Railway Company.; New York, Chicago & St. Louis Railroad.; New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Company.; New York, Ontario, and Western Railway Co.; New York, Susquehanna, and Western Railroad.; Norfolk Southern Railroad Company.; Northern Ohio Railway Company.; Northern Pacific Railroad Company.; Pennsylvania Railroad.; Pere Marquette Railroad.; Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company.; Reading Company.; Rutland Railroad Company.; Seaboard Air Line Railway Company.; Southern Pacific Railroad Company.; Southern Railway (U.S.); St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company.; St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Company.; Texas & Pacific Railway.; Union Pacific Railroad Company.; Wabash Railway Company.; Western Maryland Railway Company.; Western Pacific Railroad Company.; Western Railway of Alabama.; Wheeling and Lake Erie Railway Company.
Subjects
Railroads--Freight--United States--Maps.; Railroads--United States--Passenger traffic--Maps.; Railroads--United States--Statistics.; Railroads--United States--Traffic--Maps.
Form/Genre
Maps.
Container List
- Box 1 - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown to International and Great Northern Railroad
  - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad; Northern Ohio Railroad (Folder 1-3)
    - Freight Revenue, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Revenue, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
  - Alton Railroad, 1936 (Folder 4)
  - Ann Arbor Railroad (Folder 5)
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1936
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad (Folder 6-11)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1931
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940-1941
  - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad (Folder 12-16)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1919
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1931
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1949
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1955
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad (Folder 18-21)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
  - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad (Folder 22-24)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1919
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1939
  - Boston-Albany Railroad (Folder 25-28)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1917
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1951
    - Railroad Valuation, 1953
  - Boston and Maine Railroad (Folder 29-38)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1919
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1935
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1938
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1939
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1950
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1953
  - Buffalo, Susquehanna Railroad (Folder 39)
  - Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburgh (Folder 40)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
  - Canadian National Railroad (Folder 41-42)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
  - Canadian Pacific Railroad (Folder 43-44)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
  - Central of Georgia Railroad (Folder 43-45)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
  - Central Railroad of New Jersey (Folder 46-49)
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1954
  - Central Vermont Railroad (Folder 50-52)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad (Folder 53-57)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1921
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
  - Chicago and Alton Railroad (Folder 58)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
  - Chicago, Great Western Railroad (Folder 59-61)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad (Folder 62-74)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1950
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
    - Burlington, 1924
    - Burlington, 1934-1935
    - Burlington, 1947-1948
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad (Folder 75-78)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1952
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1954
  - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railroad (Folder 79-85)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1949-1950
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1950
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1951
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1954
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad (Folder 86-93)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Milwaukee - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Milwaukee - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1952
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railroad (Folder 94-97)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1918
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railroad (Folder 98-99)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1917
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
  - Chicago and Northwestern Railroad (Folder 100-101)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
  - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad (Folder 102-115)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1921
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
  - Cincinnati, Indianapolis and Western Railroad (Folder 116)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1918
  - Cincinnati, New Orleans and Texas Pacific Railroad (Folder 117)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1925
  - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad (Folder 118-121)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
  - Colorado and Southern Railroad (Folder 122-133)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933-1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1950
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad (Folder 134-143)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1946-1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1949
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1957
  - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad (Folder 144-147)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1921
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936-1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
  - Denver, Rio Grande and Western Railroad (Folder 148-173)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1920
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1932-1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1941
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1947-1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1949-1950
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1949-1950
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1951-1952
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1955
  - Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad (Folder 174-175)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1924
    - Railroad Valuation, 1925
  - Erie, New York, Susquehanna and Western Railroad (Folder 176-179)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1921
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
  - Erie Railroad (Folder 180-182)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948-1949
  - Florida East Coast Railroad (Folder 183-186)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
  - Grand Truck Western Railroad (Folder 187-188)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
  - Great Northern Railroad (Folder 189-193)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
  - Gulf Coast Lines (Folder 194-203)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
  - Illinois Central Railroad (Folder 204-209)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
  - Illinois Central Railroad; Yazoo and Mississippi Valley Railroad (Folder 210)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
  - International and Great Northern Railroad (Folder 211-224)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
- Box 2 - Jersey Central Lines - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad
  - Jersey Central Lines, 1948 (Folder 231)
    - Freight Traffic Density
  - Kansas City Southern Railroad (Folder 232-242)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad (Folder 259-262)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1921
    - Railroad Valuation, 1924
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936-1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
  - Louisiana-Arkansas, Louisville-Henderson, Louisville-Nashville Railroad (Folder 263-265)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
  - Louisville, Henderson and St. Louis Railroad (Folder 266)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1925
  - Maine Central Railroad (Folder 267-282)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1919
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1935
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1941
  - Michigan Central Railroad (Folder 283-287)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
  - Midland Valley Railroad (Folder 288)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1925
  - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railroad (Folder 289-292)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1936
  - Minneapolis, St. Paul and Sault St. Marie Railroad (Folder 293-321)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1949
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1950
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1952
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
  - Missouri, Kansas, Texas Railroad (Folder 322-341)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1920
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
  - Missouri and Pacific Railroad (Folder 342-356)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1953
    - Freight Traffic Density - 3784, 1956
  - Mobile and Ohio Railroad (Folder 357-358)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
  - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railroad (Folder 359-360)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
  - New York, Chicago and St. Louis (Folder 361-366)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1951
    - Missing - 363-365
  - New York and St. Louis Railroad; Lake Erie and Western Railroad (Folder 367-368)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1922
  - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad (Folder 369-373)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1918
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
  - New York, Ontario and Western Railroad (Folder 374-377)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Missing 375
  - Nortfolk and Southern Railroad (Folder 378)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
  - Northen Pacific Railroad (Folder 379-383)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Missing 383
  - Pennsylvania Railroad East of Pittsburgh and Erie (Folder 384)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1924
  - Pennsylvania Railroad - Philadelphia, Pittsburgh, Cincinnati (Folder 385)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1916
  - Pennsylvania Railroad System (Folder 386-389)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1947
    - Missing 388
  - Pere Marquette Railroad (Folder 390-393)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1916
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Missing 391
  - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad (Folder 394-396)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1951
  - Reading System (Folder 397-420)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1947
  - Rock Island, Chicago and Pacific (Folder 401-410)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1949
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1951
  - Rutland Railroad (Folder 411)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
  - Seaborn Coast Line Railroad (Folder 412-421)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1949
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1952
  - Southern Pacific System (Folder 422-428)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1945
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1952
  - Southern Railway System (Folder 429-443)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1917
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1921
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1954
  - St. Louis Southwestern Railroad (Folder 444-447)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1917
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1924
    - Railroad Valuation, 1932
  - St. Louis and San Francisco Railroad (Folder 448-451)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
  - Texas Pacific Railroad (Folder 452-456)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Missing 454-456
  - Toledo and Ohio Central Railroad (Folder 457)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
  - United States Intercoastal Traffic via Panama Canal (Folder 458-459)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
  - Union Pacific System (Folder 460-466)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
  - Virginia Railroad (Folder 467-470)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
  - Wabash Railroad (Folder 471-491)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1923
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1928
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1925
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1932
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
  - Western Maryland Railroad (Folder 492-516)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1931
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1933
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1936
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1938
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1939
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1940
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1941
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1948
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1948
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1952
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1950
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1956
  - Western Pacific Railroad (Folder 517-522)
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1934
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1934
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1935
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1935
    - Freight Traffic Density, 1937
    - Traffic Interchanged, 1937
  - Western Railroad of Alabama (Folder 523)
    - Railroad Valuation, 1925
  - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad (Folder 524 (506 on folder))
    - Railroad Valuation, 1922
  - Comparative Analysis Railroad Reports Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 1912 (Folder n/a)